(Penny:)So, we're about to shoot
this scene in the movie
(Penny:)where the killer ape DNA
is slowly taking over my body.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Penny:)But I realize they're gluing fur
everywhere except my cleavage.
(Penny:)So, I asked the director why
and he says,
"It's important
to the story that my boobs
be the last things to turn ape."
(Leonard:)It's sweet that he thinks
there's a story.
(Penny:)Oh, and there's not
even a bathroom on set.
I had to go to the gas station
across the street.
(Penny:)I mean, I was dressed
like half an ape
(Penny:)and still not even close to the
most disgusting person in there.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, I could use
your assistance.
(Leonard:)-Sure. What's up?
-Well, now that I've given up
(Sheldon:)string theory, I'm struggling
to find my next area of focus.
(Sheldon:)In your professional opinion,
(Sheldon:)which of these areas do you think
is the most promising?
(Leonard:)Well, I think there's some
really innovative stuff
(Leonard:)-going on in dark matter.
-That's helpful.
(Sheldon:)-Okay, of these four areas--
-Sheldon!